qmail.com 2003-06-05

# ForeverMail Privacy Policy

**_Last Updated: July 2, 2002_** ** __**

The ForeverMail service ("ForeverMail"), provided by Digital Footprints International  ("DFI"), has the following Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on Web pages hosted by DFI.  The terms "we" and "us" refer to DFI.

**The Information We Collect  
** This notice applies to all information collected on the ForeverMail Web site.

_Personally Identifiable Information_ **—** When visiting the ForeverMail Web site and signing up for or using ForeverMail services, you may choose to supply ForeverMail with information that identifies you personally. For Subscribers to our forwarding services, this information may include your name and e-mail address, billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, and other information. For Domain Registrants and prospective Domain Registrants, this information may include the Domain Registrant's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and other contact information billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, and other information.    
**   
** _Aggregate Information_ **—** We collect non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services. Examples of aggregate information we collect include number of views of pages on our website, counts of external websites that referred visitors to our website, popularity of services we offer, and other statistics on visits to our website.

**The Way We Use Information  
** We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as e-mail forwarding, URL forwarding or domain name registration; completing an order; processing payments; renewing an account or domain registration; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy and the ForeverMail Terms and Conditions Agreement, we do not share this information with outside parties without your express permission except to comply in responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings.

 From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to send account specific communications. Account specific communications include information that is essential for the ForeverMail service to operate properly. This includes the initial welcome mail describing features and guides to a particular service. It also includes any communications describing any changes or updates to a particular service, and renewal notices or bills. Because account specific communications are essential to providing you with the most current information on ForeverMail services these types of communications will be sent to all ForeverMail customers when appropriate. These types of communications are considered an essential part of the service for which you have subscribed and you will not be able to unsubscribe from such mailings. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above.

**Sharing your Personal Information with Other Companies  
** Except as otherwise described in this statement, DFI will NOT share your personal information with other companies.

We use a third-party called CardService International ("CardService") to process credit card transactions.  We and CardService use the information you provide solely to process the specific credit card transaction you authorize.  Your credit card number is entered on a secure web page hosted by CardService. DFI does not see or store your credit card number. You can view the CardService Privacy Policy at 

Domain registration information is provided to the domain registrar and registry as required by the appropriate domain registration agreement.  The terms of the domain registration agreements stipulate that Domain Registrant and contact information be made publicly available in the domain registrar's Whois database.  You may view those agreements here. DFI has no control over the publication of this information.

**How You Can Access or Update Your Information  
** Subscribers and Domain Registrants can access their personally identifiable information that ForeverMail collects online and maintains by logging in to their password-protected account at [http://www.forevermail.com](http://www.forevermail.com/). Subscribers and Domain Registrants can also correct factual errors in their personally identifiable information by sending us a written request that credibly documents and explains the error.

 If you have submitted information on our site but do not currently have an account with us, you can access and correct the information that we collect and maintain by contacting us and requesting such information or correction.

  To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

   **E-mail and URL Forwarding Specific Terms and Conditions  
** DFI considers e-mail transmitted via the ForeverMail service to be private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore, we will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of your private communications, except for reasons provided for in the ForeverMail Terms and Conditions Agreement.

DFI also considers the content provided at a destination web site where our URL forwarding services resolve to be the responsibility of the publisher of that web site. Therefore, we will not monitor the content of those destination web sites, except for reasons provided for in the ForeverMail Terms and Conditions Agreement.

**Use of Cookies    
**DFI does not use cookies. 

**Security of your Personal Information  
** DFI secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. DFI secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number and other financial information) is transmitted over the Internet, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Changes to this Statement  
** DFI will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When DFI posts changes to this Statement, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Statement. If there are material changes to this Statement, DFI will notify you by placing prominent notice on the ForeverMail Web site. DFI encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information. 

**How to Contact Us  
** Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us by phone (888-766-2315 ext 83), e-mail (support@forevermail.com) or postal mail (PO Box 1295, Tacoma, WA 98402).
